Before we move on, let me show you one more time this fabulous slide that describes the simple three
다음으로 넘어가기 전에 이 멋진 슬라이드를 한 번 더 보여드리죠 간단한 3개의 추상화를
abstractions and one method call to build a rag pipeline the abstractions.
묘사하고 추상화 랙 파이프라인을 구축하기 위한 하나의 메서드 호출이죠
Again, you create the LM, you create your memory.
LM을 생성하고 메모리를 생성하죠
You create your retriever just by calling your chroma vector store or whatever vector store you're working
당신은 당신의 레트리버를 생성합니다. 크로마 벡터 스토어나 .이 레트리버로 작동하는
with dot as retriever.
어떤 벡터 스토어도 호출해서요.
And then you can simply create your conversation retrieval chain with this one line passing in your
그런 다음 이 선 하나로 대화 회수 체인을 만들 수 있어요 LM, 레트리버
LM, your retriever, your memory, and you're done.
메모리로요 그럼 끝이죠
And of course, with this conversation chain you call invoke and you pass in a dictionary with your
물론 이 대화 사슬을 통해 invoke를 호출하고
question and with what you get back, you can simply call you look up the answer key and you will get
질문과 함께 사전을 전달하면 응답 키를 찾아 호출할 수 있고 모델에서
back the response from the model.
응답을 받을 수 있죠
And so with that I would say that you have leveled up your skills.
그런 점에서 실력이 한 단계 향상됐어요
You are upskilled.
기운이 넘치네요
You are now accomplished in the art of building rag pipelines.
이제 랙 파이프라인 만드는 기술을 완성했어요
Congratulations!
축하해요
You can build your own rag knowledge worker not just for a fictitious company like Endure Elm, but
자신만의 헝겊 지식 인력을 만들 수 있습니다 엔디어 엘름 같은 허구의 회사뿐
hopefully for real companies too, including your own using lamp chain.
아니라 진짜 회사에도 만들 수 있습니다 램프 체인을 사용해서요
And you can use chroma.
채도를 사용해도 돼요
You could also see how easy it is to switch that up for other vector data stores, and using models
다른 벡터 데이터 저장소를 위해 바꾸는 것도 얼마나 쉬운지 알 수 있습니다 OpenAI가 아닌
other than OpenAI, Lang chain makes that very simple indeed.
모델을 이용해 랭 체인이 아주 간단하게 만들었죠
Next time we're going to talk about lang chains declarative language briefly, it's not something we're
다음에 랑의 사슬 선언 언어를 간단히 다룰 거예요 우리가 사용할 건 아니지만
going to use, but I'll show it to you.
보여드리죠
So you could use it if you wish to.
원한다면 쓸 수 있어요
Uh, I'm going to talk a bit about how Lang Chain works under the covers, just so you have more insight.
랑 체인의 비트를 어떻게 활용하는지 알려드릴게요 여러분이 더 잘 이해하실 수 있게요
And in particular, we're going to look at a common problem with Rag, diagnose it and then talk about
특히 래그의 공통된 문제를 살펴보고 진단한 후 해결 방법을 얘기해
how to fix it.
보죠
So that will all, uh, equip you to be able to use rag in anger in production projects as you'll really
제작 프로젝트에서 랙을 사용할 수 있는 장비는 이 정도입니다 내부 작동 방식을 제대로 이해하게
understand the inner workings.
될 거예요
And with that, I will see you next time.
그럼 다음 시간에 뵙죠